练习 4-7：规则四，N 前的 held T。严格说来，held T 其实并不是
Exercise 4-7, Rule 4, held T before N. The held T is, strictly speaking, not really a
真正的 T。记住，T 和 N 在口腔里的位置非常接近。如果 T 后面紧跟 N，
T at all. Remember, T and N are very close in the mouth. If you have an N immediately
你不要爆破 T。舌头在 T 的位置，但你用
after a T, you don't pop the T. The tongue is in the T position, but you release the
N 来释放气流，而不是用 T。没有 T，也没有 schwa。特别注意不要
air with the N, not the T. There's no T and no schwa. Make a special point of not
在进入 NN 之前让舌头从上腭释放下来。
letting your tongue release from the top of your mouth before you drop into the NN.
否则，button 会听起来像两个词。非重读 T 或双写 T
Otherwise, button would sound like two words, button. An unstressed T or double T
后接 N 时要 hold 住。大声读下面这些词和句子。确保
followed by N is held. Read the following words and sentences out loud. Make sure
蓝色的 T 都被 hold 住。记住，N 前没有 uh 音。注意，
that the blue T's are held. Remember, there is no uh sound before the N. Note,
另一个要记住的点是，你需要一个清晰向上滑动的语调，一直上到
another point to remember is that you need a sharp upward sliding intonation, up to
held T，然后在 N 上快速下降。只要到 T 的位置，然后哼出声。
the held T, then a quick drop for the N. Just go to the T position and hum.
Written, written, sentence, forgotten, certain, curtain, mitten, Martin, bitten,
button, kitten, mutant, latent, mountain, recently, lately, partly, frequently. One,
he's forgotten the carton of satin mittens. Two, she's certain that he has
written it. Three, the cotton curtain is not in the fountain. Four, the hikers went
in the mountains. Five, Martin has gotten a kitten. Six, students study Latin in
Britain. Seven, Whitney has a patent on those sentences. Eight, he has not
forgotten what was written about the mutant on the mountain. Nine, it's not
certain that it was gotten from the fountain. Ten, you need to put an orange
cotton curtain on that window. Eleven, we that certain satin better than the carton
of cotton curtains. 12. The Intercontinental Hotel is in Seattle. 13.
The frightened witness had forgotten the important written message. 14. The child
wasn't beaten because he had bitten the button.